<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Jillian Caplan</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/media/icon_huc5ddbc9f1a0fc66ccf7e7751fffdaeef_427515_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Flourish Workshop</title>
      <link>/project/the-flourish-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/the-flourish-workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Flourish Workshop is a 45-minute interactive presentation designed for university students. The workshop consists of three parts: A) psychoeducation, B) strategies to flourish, and C) strategies to reduce stigma surrounding mental health issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wellmtl.ca&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;WellMTL.ca&lt;/a&gt; to see all of our workshops or
email &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info.wellmtl@gmail.com&#34;&gt;info.wellmtl@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; to book a talk!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concordia&#39;s Journal of Psychology and Neuroscience</title>
      <link>/project/cjpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/cjpn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Effective communication is an indispensable mechanism that allows scientific inquiry to continue flourishing. As such, learning the necessary skills to effectively communicate science is a crucial tool for any young scientist. The Concordia Journal of Psychology and Neuroscience seeks to enhance student life at Concordia University by providing students in the psychology department with unique opportunities in scientific communication, peer-reviewing, and editing. Hopefully, these experiences will enrich their understanding of the scientific process and benefit their future careers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We offer students a traditional route to publishing their research by preparing a scientific manuscript and going through a peer-review process with fellow undergraduate and graduate students in psychology. Graduate students serve as Editors and Reviewers, ensuring that each manuscript is scientifically accurate and eloquently written. CJPN also provides senior undergraduates with editorial experience, specifically, with the opportunity to become a peer-reviewer. These select undergraduate reviewers, in collaboration with graduate student reviewers, will gain sought-after professional skills, as well as an inside look of how the peer review process is conducted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for our &lt;strong&gt;first edition&lt;/strong&gt;, which will be published to our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.concordiapsychjournals.ca/cjpn/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; in September 2021!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pose for Hope</title>
      <link>/project/pose-for-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/pose-for-hope/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;-UPDATE-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The event was a huge success! Thank you so much to everyone who participated, donated, or sponsored the event. Together, we raised over $10,000 for the Eating Disorders Continuum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out this small video of the event that we made for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://rjcfoundation.ca/news/pose-for-hope/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Raymond James Canada Foundation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-ORIGINAL-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started Pose for Hope, along with a recovered patient and friend who wanted to give back to the clinic that helped her heal. The Eating Disorders Continuum (EDC) at the Douglas Mental Health Institute supports countless patients who are struggling with eating disorders and mental health issues. Right now, they need our help!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through this fun yoga event, we aim to build hope for patients who are seeking treatment or support, but have yet to receive the help they need. Due to under-funding, so many patients are relegated to the waitlist. Our goal is to raise funds for the EDC, to help the clinic increase patient care. Everyone should have the chance to get help. No one should have to battle these illnesses alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pose for Hope event will raise funds to help the &lt;a href=&#34;https://fondationdouglas.qc.ca/projects/programme-troubles-alimentaires-parmi-plus-importants-monde/?lang=en&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Eating Disorders Continuum&lt;/a&gt; of the Douglas Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How do I participate?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit our &lt;a href=&#34;https://fondationdouglas.akaraisin.com/ui/poseforhope&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;web page&lt;/a&gt; to register! (Note: the page has now been taken down)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Consider creating or joining a team.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start fundraising - encourage family and friends to join your team or sponsor you with a donation! Participants who raise $50 will have a spot reserved for them at the event.
If you are not interested in attending, you may sponsor the event by donating to a team of your choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;When and where?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday, September 26th from 1:30 p.m. to 3:30 p.m. at Pierre Elliott Trudeau Park (6975 Chemin Mackle, Côte Saint-Luc, QC, H4W 3A5)
Yoga mats and snacks will be provided
Please note that proper protocols for COVID-19 will be implemented. For those who feel more comfortable participating from home, we will be offering a &lt;strong&gt;virtual link to the event via Zoom&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, let’s build &lt;em&gt;hope&lt;/em&gt; for mental health!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
