<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science Communication | Jillian Caplan</title>
    <link>/tag/science-communication/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tag/science-communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Science Communication</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/media/icon_huc5ddbc9f1a0fc66ccf7e7751fffdaeef_427515_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Science Communication</title>
      <link>/tag/science-communication/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concordia&#39;s Journal of Psychology and Neuroscience</title>
      <link>/project/cjpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/cjpn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Effective communication is an indispensable mechanism that allows scientific inquiry to continue flourishing. As such, learning the necessary skills to effectively communicate science is a crucial tool for any young scientist. The Concordia Journal of Psychology and Neuroscience seeks to enhance student life at Concordia University by providing students in the psychology department with unique opportunities in scientific communication, peer-reviewing, and editing. Hopefully, these experiences will enrich their understanding of the scientific process and benefit their future careers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We offer students a traditional route to publishing their research by preparing a scientific manuscript and going through a peer-review process with fellow undergraduate and graduate students in psychology. Graduate students serve as Editors and Reviewers, ensuring that each manuscript is scientifically accurate and eloquently written. CJPN also provides senior undergraduates with editorial experience, specifically, with the opportunity to become a peer-reviewer. These select undergraduate reviewers, in collaboration with graduate student reviewers, will gain sought-after professional skills, as well as an inside look of how the peer review process is conducted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for our &lt;strong&gt;first edition&lt;/strong&gt;, which will be published to our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.concordiapsychjournals.ca/cjpn/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; in September 2021!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
